orangeshark.com 2008-12-16

# Play Free Online Games, Win Prizes & Socialize

OrangeShark.com is a member based skill games tournament site.  Our members are the most valuable part of our business.  We establish trust in our members by ensuring that all members find OrangeShark.com a fair and unbiased place to play, a place to have fun playing game, and a site where their personal information is secure and private.  The below document describes the Privacy Policy we extended to our members and visitors who visit OrangeShark.com. 

**OrangeShark.com Privacy Policy**  
OrangeShark.com (herein referred to as “this site”, “OrangeShark.com” or “Orange Shark” or “we”) is fully owned and managed by Orange Shark, a USA based company. Visitors on this site and members on this site will be herein referred to as “you”, “your”, “users”, “visitors” or “members”.  By visiting this site, interacting with this site and its content, playing any of the games, and becoming a member, you agree to the Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  
**Go to top**  
  
**What types of information do we collect?** **  
** User information is collected in different parts of this site.  The following describes overview of what is collected. 

_Personal Information (herein referred to as “Personal Information”):_

is personally identifiable information about you as an individual collected through this site. This information can include your full name, address, email address, telephone number, date of birth, sex, your picture, Paypal account information, credit card information social security number (for USA citizens filing Form 1099) and any other information that identifies you as you. 

_General Information (herein referred to as “General information”):_

this includes your computer hardware, your computer’s IP address, your internet provider, downloaded files, operating system, web browser, geographic point of connectivity, player rating and activity level, winnings, cash payouts, communication with this site via email, mail, chat, support request and phone.

_Anonymous Information (herein referred to as “Anonymous Information”):_ is information collected through this site which does not identify you as a specific individual. This information includes data regarding your game play pattern, your deposit preferences, your buddy list, your advertisement views and your account balance.  
**Go to top**  
  
**Where information is collected and how it is used?**  
The below section details where we collect user information.  Areas where information is collected and is not mentioned below also fall under this section of privacy policy by default.

 _OrangeShark.com invitation page:_

  On these pages users are able to input their email address and password to access their address book.  Once the email account is accessed, the user can view and select contacts in their address to which they want this site to send an invitation email on their behalf.  During this process, we save the user’s full name to include in the emails sent to their address book contact list; we save the user’s contact list for emailing; and we do not save the user’s email passwords.

_Registration and Sign up pages:_

  On these pages users will be required to enter their personal information, a user name and other items in order to create an account with us.

 _Deposits:_

During deposits, users will be required to enter their personal information, including credit card and it’s billing address and if needed the user’s Paypal information.

 _Sponsor Offers:_

  Users can choose to interact with Sponsor Offers on our site.  Sponsors are advertiser who credit user’s with funds in their account in exchange user submitting their personal information and other information. During this interaction, the user approves us to input the user’s personal information into the sponsor requested data fields.  The sponsor may also request additional information from the user.  Sponsor’s have their own Privacy and Terms of usage policy.  We recommend you review their policies before interacting with them.  It is the user’s responsibility to review the sponsors privacy terms and terms and conditions before completing the Sponsor’s required information request to the user.

 _Internal Marketing:_

From time to time, OrangeShark.com will email to users or present to users additional registration data, conduct a survey, newsletters, information and conduct phone reviews and opinion session.

_General Emails:_ User will receive emails from OrangeShark.com regarding their account, account status updates, customer support emails, account balance and finance emails, buddy request emails, entry fees, provide user requested information, challenge status, and challenge emails.  
_Form 1099_ : This applies to visitors and members from areas under jurisdiction of USA.  All USA tax payers are required by the IRS (Internal Revenue Service) to report your total winnings on OrangeShark in any given calendar year reach a total of $600.00.  When this amount is reached in your account, OrangeShark will request that you submit your social security number in order to send you a Form 1099.  Failure to provide your social security number at that time will prevent you from participating in game challenges.  
_Legal Compliance:_   We comply with all regulations and laws of USA.  If requested by legal authorities, we will hand over personal information of the user. _

Other uses:

_ OrangeShark may use user’s full name, username, email id, feedback/suggestions and address for internal marketing promotions.  We hide or mask certain information to keep the user’s information safe.   
  
**Go to top**  
  
**Where is the information held?**   
OrangeShark collects stores and uses information it stores in protected servers based in USA. 

**Unsubscribing from emails sent by OrangeShark:** **  
** Users can unsubscribe from any single or multiple emails sent by OrangeShark. To unsubscribe please follow the unsubscribe link on the bottom of any of our emails. Your request is processed immediately. No further mailings will be sent to you.   Please note, on the unsubscribe page, you may be given options to unsubscribe for 1 or many different types of emails we send.  You will only be unsubscribed from the one you selected.   
**Go to top**  
  
**Technology Used by OrangeShark** **  
**_SSL_ :  SSL stands for Secure Sockets Layer.  This is an encryption technology used by OrangeShark to secure user’s information during transmission of certain personal information.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be assured to be absolutely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted over the Internet. 

_Cookies:_ are pieces of data files stored in your computer’s “temporary internet files” folder. This technology is completely safe and almost every site on the internet uses them.  These are used by OrangeShark.com to track user’s site behavior, fraud tracking, for anonymous data collection, and for tracking used to improve our site’s performance for individual users.  
**Go to top**  
  
**Viewing and reviewing your Personal Information?**  
Users can view and edit their personal information by logging into their OrangeShark account, then clicking on My Account and My Info.  We request user’s input valid and accurate information in this page.  Fraudulent or incorrect information can result in customer support issues, proper crediting of deposits and other issues.  
  
**Go to top**  
  
**Online Chat Rooms and Profiles**   
You may choose to disclose information, including personal information, about yourself in our online chat rooms, message boards, user “profiles” for public view or in similar forums on our sites. Information that you disclose in any of these forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Please see our Terms of Service on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on our web sites.   
  
**Go to top**  
  
**How to protect your account and personal information:** **  
**_Keeping your account login private:_   don’t share your account information with anyone.  Your account contains your personal information and might contain cash balances.  This should be kept secure.

_Log Out:_ when not using the software, log out of it.  Others may be able to access your account if you leave yourself logged into your account.  
**Go to top**  
  
**Other Privacy Policies:**  
**Links to Third Party Web Sites and Third Party Advertisements**  
This site may contain hyperlinks to other Internet web sites or third party advertisements. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such web sites, advertisers, or third parties, or for the content of such sites or advertisements. It is possible that these links or advertisements, themselves, may be used by third parties or others to collect personal or other information about visitors to this site. It is solely the visitor's obligation to review and understand the privacy practices and policies of these other Web sites and of these advertisers and third parties.  
  
**Go to top**  
  
**Changes in Privacy Policy**  
This site updates its Privacy Policy and Terms from time to time.  The users of this site will not be notified regarding these changes.  It is the user’s responsibility to check from time to time to see if there are any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Any such change, revision, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on this site.  
  
**Go to top**  
  
**Questions or Concerns:**  
We hope the above Privacy Policy was clear and gave you a better understanding of how you information is used and how we keep it safe.  If you have any further concerns or questions, please click on the following link to access our contact page. 

Contact Us:   <http://games.orangeshark.com/contact_us.php>

**Thank You,**  
OrangeShark Staff  
  
Close
